{
    "subject": "resource/Born_in_East_L.A._(song)",
    "predicate": "ontology/musicalArtist",
    "object": "resource/Cheech_&_Chong",
    "human_readable": "The musical artist of Born in East L.A. (song) is Cheech & Chong.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9775550365447998,
            "question": "Is 'Born in East L.A.' a popular song by Cheech & Chong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9692344665527344,
            "question": "Who are the musical artists behind the song 'Born in East L.A.'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.966518223285675,
            "question": "Where was the musical act Cheech & Chong born in East L.A. referencing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8475719690322876,
            "question": "What is the genre of the song 'Born in East L.A.'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8453130125999451,
            "question": "What is the main theme of the song 'Born in East L.A.'"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8431382179260254,
            "question": "Do Cheech & Chong have any other famous songs besides 'Born in East L.A.'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8096868395805359,
            "question": "What is the name of the song associated with Cheech & Chong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7681146264076233,
            "question": "What type of music are Cheech & Chong known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5750814080238342,
            "question": "What year was 'Born in East L.A.' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.039266493171453476,
            "question": "Which duo is known for their comedic songs about cannabis culture?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The musical artist of Born in East L.A. (song) is Cheech & Chong.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3661_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was 'Born in East L.A.' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3661_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of music are Cheech & Chong known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3661_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the song associated with Cheech & Chong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3661_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3661_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3661_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3661_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3661_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3661_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3661_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3661_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3661_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3661_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3661_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided context mentions that \"Born in East L.A.\" is a song by Cheech and Chong, which supports the statement that the musical artist of \"Born in East L.A. (song)\" is Cheech & Chong."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}